(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-25T22:39:44.157794",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
The stars aligned like it was always meant to be
So come along and join me, embracing serendipity
One shooting star, one blaze of light
Once in a lifetime
One million wishes in the night
Somehow, my dearest dream came true
Once in a lifetime
I saw this brilliant sky with you
So many roads,
so many journeys
But luck decided that today we'd meet
It's serendipity
Ah...
Mysterious, a single moment changes fate
The winds and tides that shaped our lives all led us to this day
It's wondrous, somehow we met along the way
Now here you are beside me, embracing serendipity
Once in a lifetime
That's right
One magic moment that we share
Once in a lifetime
While music lingers in the air
A song of everlasting bonds
Once in a lifetime
To warm my heart as time goes on
Each day will bring
another journey
With new encounters that are meant to be
It's serendipity
Ah...
Miraculous, that we're together in this life
A perfect dance of happenstance that brought us side by side
It's marvelous that though the universe is wide
You're standing here beside me, embracing serendipity
Once in a lifetime
That's right
This is right where we're meant to be
Sweet, sweet serendipity
Wishing on stars and chasing after dreams,
seeing where they lead
Say it with me, everybody
Serendipity
Mysterious...
Mysterious, a single moment changes fate
The winds and tides that shaped our lives all led us to this day
It's wondrous, somehow we met along the way
Now here you are beside me, embracing serendipity
We'll shine like shooting stars in flight tonight
Once in a lifetime
That's right
The stars aligned like it was always meant to be
So come along and join me, embracing serendipity
One shooting star, one blaze of light
Once in a lifetime
One million wishes in the night
Somehow, my dearest dream came true
Once in a lifetime
I saw this brilliant sky with you
So many roads,
so many journeys
Greetings, CC, my fated rival.
Greetings, Ina, my destined rival!
And hello to every...
Everyone watching from...
Serendipity!
Remember, if you want a chance for your wish to be featured on the Otomo or the Takodachi that we made...
Post about it with #WishUponTakoTomo!
Yay! Thank you amiami for supporting our rivalry...
and for supporting Serendipity!
Be sure to check out their booth at Anime Expo!
Yay!
Hey Pebbles!
It's Koseki Bijou!
And all of hololive BASE is here with me!
All 14 of us!
hololive BASE is coming to Round1 USA locations nationwide,
starting this September!
Come hang out with us!
Follow @round1usa on Instagram and X so you don't miss out on any updates!
We can't wait to see you there!
Bye-bye!
The stars aligned like it was always meant to be
So come along and join me, embracing serendipity
Serendipity
One shooting star, one blaze of light
(One time in a lifetime)
One million wishes in the night
Somehow, my dearest dream came true
(One time in a lifetime)
I saw this brilliant sky with you
So many roads, so many journeys
But luck decided that today we'd meet
It's serendipity
Ah...
Mysterious, a single moment changes fate
The winds and tides that shaped our lives all led us to this day
It's wondrous, somehow we met along the way
Now here you are beside me, embracing serendipity
One time in a lifetime
(That's right)
One magic moment that we share
(One time in a lifetime)
While music lingers in the air
A song of everlasting bonds
(One time in a lifetime)
To warm my heart as time goes on
Each day will bring another journey
With new encounters that are meant to be
It's serendipity
Ah...
Miraculous, that we're together in this life
A perfect dance of happenstance that brought us side by side
It's marvelous that though the universe is wide
You're standing here beside me, embracing serendipity
One time in a lifetime
(That's right)
This is right where we're meant to be
(Sweet, sweet serendipity)
Wishing on stars and chasing after dreams, seeing where they lead
Say it with me, everybody
(Serendipity)
Mysterious
Mysterious, a single moment changes fate
The winds and tides that shaped our lives all led us to this day
(Oh, ah)
It's wondrous, somehow we met along the way
Now here you are beside me, embracing serendipity
We'll shine like shooting stars
In flight tonight
One time in a lifetime
(That's right)
Attention For Visitors
The concert will be starting soon. 開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon. Please wait a moment until the show starts.
Attention For Visitors
The concert will be starting soon.
A-D-V-E-N-T
Everyone! Let's make some noise!
Time to get this party started!
Fire, fire, light the fire, brighter, higher, as you desire
Chasing all that we aspire
Spreading out like wildfire
Never ever have I ever been a sinner, been a winner
Take the chance and with my lighter
Start the fire!
Counting down
I know the secret to this overkilling, sad old stories burying me down
Step out of the system, break out, giving everything
This is our time, we're on to discover
Hello, brand new world, would you welcome the light?
Unfreeze eyes from long night
Fire, fire, light the fire, brighter, higher, as you desire, night is beating heart
Jump into the flame of life
新しい世界へ
To a brand new world
Jump until the end of time
次元の向こう側 連れてってあげる
I'll take you to the other side of dimension
Rebellion!
I know that I can still be the future of this story
I know that I can be free
The one and the only
They tell me that I'm crazy
I'll never let them stop me
This is our epic...
Time to get this party started
Never ever have I ever
Been a sinner, been a winner
Fire, fire, light the fire, fire, fire, light the fire
Night is beating heart
Jump into the flame of life
新しい世界へ
To a brand new world
Jump until the end of time
次元の向こう側 連れてってあげる
I'll take you to the other side of dimension
Jump into the flame of life
それぞれのステージへ
To our respective stages
Jump until the end of time
奇跡の向こう側 連れてってあげる
I'll take you to the other side of miracles
Rebellion!
Time to get this party started, fire, fire, light the fire, fire, fire as you desire, time to get this party started!
Don't, don't know me, unpredictable
Takin' you all below, takin' you all be-
Don't, don't know me, irresistible
Takin' you all below, below, below we go
They think they want it, huh? They wanna get, get some
Then we take them down, down, down
Waiting at the borderline
Run, it's no surprise
You ain't gonna win, but you can try
I told ya you're gonna know us
End up in my lineup
Listen, listen
Run and hide and scream out loud, already locked ya out
This game you always play
Call me corrupt, won't hear anything
Aiming my sights down right on your heart
Throwing the keys out, shut down night, night, night
Judge, lover, executioner! No place to hide, no way to run, you're just done
Look high, run right, now suffer, you die!
Shinin' on the edge
Don't, don't know me, unpredictable, typical of you
Gonna let it go
So you think you're on my level? No, you'll never know, as above, so traditional!
Woohoo! Look, have we got it? Hey!
Right in the line of my view
What's wrong, what's right?
Lost in a fantasy
Want to be diseased?
Show that you will never make it out
Eyes front right now
And do it, do it, 逃げたって無駄に にゃお にゃお, and the music gotta loud clear
And do it, do it, it's useless to run, meow meow, and the music gotta loud clear
See your guilty heart
We're not gonna stop, it's just us
JUSTICE!
Get down, get down, hit that
Run like that, run like that
Get down, get down, down, down, down!
Lock you up, let go, swing up off the low
Telling you, already know, don't check in, know it
Right in the line of my view
What's wrong, what's right with you?
Right in the night of my view
Come take a bite
Never ending in the dark! Judge, lover, executioner!
Just...
No one to trust, we get...
Get, get, get!
We rise!
Yeah!
Standing on the edge, don't know me, I'm unpredictable, typical for you
Got nowhere to go, show you something real, mine
Level up, you'll never know, you'll never know, as above, so below
Below you should know
So let's get, just up, level up, unpredictable, beautiful, just look up
Look up, look up
Don't mess, level up, almost criminal, as above, so below
Below
離散
[Title: 離散]
Ready?
That's good, game water, Champagne, players here, all complain, why me? No, not again, shout out to town, but
In the time, so dry those eyes
Look around, what satisfies
The broken and bruised
I got something to prove now
Abracadabra, let's go
Watch them like dice as they fall
끝까지 가볼까? 나를 막진 못해!
Shall we go to the end? You can't stop me!
Top of the, top of the world
And learning to light up the way to overall
Or die
We hit that high
Straight out, mistake us
Come on now, don't be shy
뜨겁게 달아올라
Heating up hot
Run up all day, all night
So turn it up!
Can't stop, won't stop, reachin'
Can'stop, won't stop, reachin'
Who said the sky's the limit?
Showed them that we mean business
We are the young and vicious
They can't, they never lie
Fly high with pride and leave your fears behind
Check on me, 우리는 계속해서 party
Check on me, we continue to party
불을 붙여, what's standard party
Light the fire, what's standard party
Baddie, baddie, nobody can stop me, 꾸물거리다가
Baddie, baddie, nobody can stop me, while hesitating
Go, go, go, bilingual
Acting, 언니, 스타트, plus, my journey
Acting, unnie, start, plus, my journey
멋지지 않아?
Isn't it cool?
Shit, and off goes around
Shoot your mouth, it will come right down, ready the fight
Ready the screaming
Abracadabra, let's go
Watch how we're ripping it up
거기 서서 뭐 하는지, 다 돌려 대며, play
What are you doing standing there, turning it all, play
Raising up demons
Believe in the beat and just wait
And see
We hit that high
Straight out, mistake us
Come on now, don't be shy
뜨겁게 달아올라
Heating up hot
Run up all day, all night
Let me hear you holler, let's bring it on
Go, we go hard
Go, go, hard
이 순간을 즐겨, 원한다면 go
Enjoy this moment, if you want it, go
We go hard
I want it all
즐겨봐, 함께 가, just stay
Enjoy it, let's go together, just stay
듣기만 하지 말고, 골라
Don't just listen, choose
Monster, 맞아, 시작이야
Monster, that's right, this is the start
끝까지 달려가
Run until the end
We'll hit...
We hit that high
Straight out, mistake us
Come on now, don't be shy
가슴이 터져버릴 듯하게
Like my heart is about to burst
멈출 수 없어, 같이 dance all night
Can't stop, let me dance all night with you
Don't be afraid of losing
It's just a new beginning
Look at the clouds we're in
Sometimes it takes a villain
They got the time is nigh
Fly high with pride and leave your fears behind
High
業
[Title: 業]
Cut your other ties
This ain't the only battlefield that can televise
Ego is enormous, so put the camera down and face it
They win and got complacent
Kill and run with me
You say you stand for nothing no one else can relate
Just know the company you keep is in the business of hate, are you...
Afraid? Run away?
I'm close to getting you
I've been dancing on my own in a bulletproof vest
Go shoot shoot shoot 'em out, baby, doesn't matter
Disguise... ricochet
You can think about me, I need time
Or money time
So get your street fight!
This is trench war!
I'll make you march, march, march till you hit the floor!
Getting thirsty for collision, let 'em wonder what they're missing in the front row
Now here we go! Seen a white line
It's the call to arms
They come to listen, the unforgiven, make a decision as you're looking for permission
To riot, you got it wrong
Think about it, your identity clickbaits, now you're alone
Tear... Liar...
Safe for nothing, play the coward, stand for someone, you'll devour
It's a sick, twisted, mess-created existence!
Tear... Liar...
Safe for nothing, play the coward, stand for someone, you'll devour
It's a sick, twisted, mess-created existence!
てめぇの所為で
Because of you!
WASTE!
ツラも汚すぎて
Your face is way too filthy,
この子に決めた
I've decided on this one.
角度を調整
Adjusting the angle,
角度微調整
fine-tuning the angle.
飽き足らぬ声から
From an insatiable voice,
プレイス・エニィ・ベスト
Place any best,
実感するすれ違い
feeling the passing of paths.
It's absurd
Can't stop the sound
才能最高!
Talent is supreme!
交差する旅路よ
O crossing journeys,
あつまったら
when we gather,
交差いただくわ
I'll take the intersection.
時間が無駄無駄や
Time is such a waste!
じゃあね! じゃあ!
Bye then! Bye!
I can tell you're not a threat
舌が回る
My tongue moves fast,
口走ったら最後
if it slips, it's the end.
誰になりそう?
Who might I become?
何にもなりそう
I could become anything.
退屈なロンリー・ロンリー
Boring, lonely, lonely,
自分を許せば
if I forgive myself,
I'm ultimate, yeah
体を伸ばしてみくだして
Stretch out my body and look down on them.
Hey war, hey war, hey war, oh
Say again!
才能最高!
Talent is supreme!
ハデに決めろや
Show off flashily!
散々ですね
How terrible, isn't it?
I can tell that that's a threat
じゃあね! じゃあ! I'm the one that's not impressed
Bye then! Bye! I'm the one that's not impressed.
てめぇの所為で
Because of you!
先手必勝の払い
A preemptive strike to pay them back,
ぱっと咲いて何事もなく
blooming brightly without a hitch.
We're not rivals!
We're not equals!
I gotta tell you
I never liked you
Now, would I lie to you?
Let me ignite you
Base instincts take control
Like primal ways of a warrior
Is it glory you're after, like me?
Underestimated everywhere I turn
Taking aim, but it doesn't make a difference at all
I got a million different enemies I cannot recall
You're rocking up to a battle when you know that you'll fall
Hidden motivation, watch it all burn
I gotta tell you
I never liked you
Now, would I lie to you?
Not yet...
When thunder crashes down
When the world caves under my pressure, there'll be no one to save
Where is your pride, your human will to survive?
Was it just empty words for your grave?
I reach inside this soul
Now all that remains is delusion and decay
'Cause of you, I live this way
We're not rivals!
We're not equals!
Lately I realized I would never be, never be alone
It was always right in front of me
Do you know? Do you remember, remember
How we used to be so carefree?
I can feel...
I can feel the rain wash over you
Us, yeah
Can you hear my heart like thunder?
Upside down 들리는 내 목소리
Upside down, my voice is heard
I've got to make a move, make a move
So far I could not break through the cage I'm in
And I don't know how to reach for you
Hardly ever get a chance to speak alone
Could it ever be, can't you feel it too?
Side by side we could laugh all through our days
Baby, just let me make my way to you
Can't make them stop, hidden sparks inside ignite and flare up
And when we talk, all my secrets spilling over the top
So when I step up to your side and my heart is beating in double time
In every moment you make me feel alive, it goes like
I can feel the rain wash over you
Us, yeah
Can you hear my heart like thunder?
Upside down 들리는 내 목소리
Upside down, my voice is heard
I've got to make a move, make a move
So far I could not break through the cage I'm in
I don't know how to reach for you
Hardly ever get a chance to speak alone
Could it ever be, can't you feel it too?
Side by side we could laugh all through our days
Baby, just let me make my way to you
Hardly ever get a chance to speak alone
Could it ever be, can't you feel it too?
Side by side we could laugh all through our days
Baby, just let me make my way to you
Hello, L.A.!
Hi!
Hello, hello, hello!
Hello up there!
Hello down there!
Hello, 皆さん!
Hello, everyone!
Hey, who are you?
Hiya, darlings! This is Hololive English -Advent-'s devilish diva...
...the one, the only, Nerissa Ravencroft!
And with me...
Roses are red, the fire of my heart is blue. Also known as the Scarlet Queen,
the Harbinger of Order, Leader of Justice...
I am Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame!
Lovely to see you! Lovely!
L.A.!
Wow! What a setlist thus far, huh?
I know! We're starting off really strong!
We had... SNEAKERS! SNEAKERS!
Whoa!
And we had Mori rocking it out!
Seriously! And then Kronii coming in with her new song! So good!
Yeah, such cute dance moves!
And we had Advent and Justice, of course!
Yes, yes! Did you enjoy?
And, hey, did you enjoy the music so far?
Yeah!
Wow! You know what? We didn't have solos yesterday.
No, no. So we must be having them today, right?
So excited!
Oh, yeah! For mine, I want to practice something, okay?
A little chant from Great Exardia.
So when I go "Oggi Oggi Oggi", you go "Oi! Oi! Oi!"
Are you ready?
Okay!
Here we go! Oggi Oggi Oggi!
Perfect! 完璧!
Perfect! Absolute perfection!
How about you? Any sneak peeks about your solo?
Hmm, would you guys really like a sneak peek?
Well, uh, I think I have to remind you all...
...no matter how you identify, no matter what you are...
...you in this audience today...
...are my wives! Can I hear it from my wives?!
What the freak?! Everyone here is your wife too?
Including you!
So, if I ask you to sing along, you have to, all right?
You've got to.
Well, yeah, that's my hint. Does it give it away?
Maybe a little.
You know, we're singing, and I was thinking that...
We'd like to hear you guys sing, too.
You guys know I like harmonies!
So we're gonna split you into different notes, okay?
You guys over here,
you guys over here,
and all of you at the top!
So, we're gonna start off with you guys here. We want you to hold this note.
Perfect!
You guys...
Up there...
All right, everyone together!
Oh, beautiful! Beautiful!
Oh my gosh, we have our own choir!
So good!
We gotta do that more often, that was cool!
Yeah, I like hearing you all sing for us!
Hey, that reminds me of a song, doesn't it? You know that first note?
Three, two, one...
It's wonderful,
somehow we met along the way.
Now here you are beside me,
embracing serendipity!
Wow, that was great, wasn't it?
It's wonderful harmonizing with you.
And I just wanna say, thank you so much for being my friend.
I love you!
We get to sing together!
I'm so excited! I'm so excited!
I'm just too happy! I'm so happy!
I love you!
Oh, I stemmed too fast! There we go.
無料配信は次の曲で最後になります。
This free stream will end after the next song.
ライブの続きはぜひ配信チケットを買ってみてね！
Be sure to buy a stream ticket to watch the rest of the live concert!
The YouTube free sneak peek is only until the next song, which is...
...a duet!
If you want to continue watching, click the link in the description and get your tickets now!
All right, everybody!
On three, we all say "Serendipity", got it?
Aw, thank you so very much! We love you guys so much!
We love you!
All right, here we go!
Three, two, one... Serendipity!
Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame
Nerissa Ravencroft
Bloodraven
残酷な天使のように
Like a cruel angel,
少年よ 神話になれ
young boy, become a legend!
蒼い風がいま
Even if a clear blue wind now
胸のドアを叩いても
knocks on the door of your heart,
私だけをただ見つめて
you just smile, looking straight at me,
微笑んでるあなた
smiling softly...
そっとふれるもの
Too involved in yearning for
求めることに夢中で
something soft to touch,
運命さえまだ知らない
your innocent eyes
いたいけな瞳
still know nothing of fate yet.
だけどいつか気付くでしょう
But someday you will surely realize
その背中には
that on your back,
遥か未来めざすための
there are wings meant to guide you
羽根があること
toward the far future.
残酷な天使のテーゼ
A cruel angel's thesis
窓辺からやがて飛び立つ
will soon take flight through the window,
ほとばしる熱いパトスで
with surging, hot pathos!
思い出を裏切るなら
If you betray your memories,
この空を抱いて輝く
Embracing this sky, shining bright,
少年よ 神話になれ
Young boy, become a legend!
ずっと眠ってる わたしの愛のゆりかご
Sleeping forever in the cradle of my love,
あなただけが 夢の使者に呼ばれる朝がくる
The morning comes when only you are called by the messenger of dreams.
細い首筋を 月明かりが映している
The moonlight shines upon your slender neck.
世界中の時間を止めて 閉じ込めたいけど
I want to stop time all over the world and lock it away, but...
もしも二人出会えたことに意味があるなら
If there is a meaning to the two of us meeting,
わたしはそう 自由を知るためのバイブル
I am, yes, a bible for learning what freedom is.
残酷な天使のテーゼ 悲しみが蒸して始まる
A cruel angel's thesis, and then sadness begins.
抱きしめた命の形 その夢に目覚めたとき
The shape of life I held close, when I wake up to that dream,
誰よりも光を放つ 少年よ神話になれ
Shining brighter than anyone else, young boy, become a legend!
人は愛を紡ぎながら 歴史をつくる
People create history while weaving love together.
女神なんてなれないまま わたしは生きる
Unable to ever become a goddess, I live on.
残酷な天使のテーゼ 窓辺からやがて飛び立つ
A cruel angel's thesis soon flies forth from the window,
ほとばしる熱いパトスで 思い出を裏切るなら
If you betray your memories with surging, hot pathos,
この空を抱いて輝く 少年よ神話になれ
Embracing this sky, shining bright, young boy, become a legend!
The stars aligned like it was always meant to be
So come along and join me, embracing serendipity
One shooting star, one blaze of light
One time in a lifetime
One million wishes in the night
Somehow, my dearest dream came true
One time in a lifetime
I saw this brilliant sky with you
So many roads, so many journeys
But luck decided that today we'd meet
It's serendipity
Mysterious, a single moment changes fate
The winds and tides that shaped our lives all led us to this day
It's wondrous, somehow we met along the way
Now here you are beside me, embracing serendipity
One time in a lifetime (that's right)
One time in a lifetime
One magic moment that we share
While music lingers in the air
A song of everlasting bonds
One time in a lifetime
To warm my heart as time goes on
Each day will bring another journey
With new encounters that are meant to be
It's serendipity
Miraculous, that we're together in this life
A perfect dance of happenstance that brought us side by side
It's marvelous that though the universe is wide
You're standing here beside me, embracing serendipity
One time in a lifetime (that's right)
One time in a lifetime
This is right where we're meant to be
Sweet, sweet serendipity
Wishing on stars and chasing after dreams
Seeing where they lead
Say it with me, everybody!
Serendipity!
Mysterious, a single moment changes fate
The winds and tides that shaped our lives all led us to this day
It's wondrous, somehow we met along the way